<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cake</title>
    <link>https://cakedefi.com/de/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cake</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Alle Rechte vorbehalten</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cakedefi.com/de/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Imprint</title>
      <link>https://cakedefi.com/de/imprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cakedefi.com/de/imprint/</guid>
      <description> Impressum Cake Pte. Ltd   Land der Registrierung Singapore   UEN 201918368M   Contact   E-Mail-Addresse team@cakedefi.com   der Aufsichtsrat   Dr. Julian Hosp Exekutivdirektor und Vorsitzender   U-Zyn Chua Geschäftsführer   John Rost Aufsichtsratmitglied   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Press Materials</title>
      <link>https://cakedefi.com/de/press/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cakedefi.com/de/press/</guid>
      <description> Press Materials Here are some assets you can use when you talk about us and to link back to us.
Logos Cake Logos    Download Cake logo       Download the Slice     Pool Logos    Download Pool logo     Colors  #5B10FF
R91 G16 B255
C77 M77 Y0 K0
    Please ✅  Use the Cake logotype to link to Cake Use the Pool logotype to link to Pool Use the Slice mark when space is constrained Use the logos in a blog post or news article about Cake or Pool  Please don&amp;rsquo;t ❌  Use the logos as your own logo Create a modified version of the logos Put our logos in your own logo Sell our logo Change the colors and add your own text/images  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://cakedefi.com/de/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cakedefi.com/de/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy Cake Pte Ltd. takes the privacy of your information seriously. This Privacy Policy applies to the cakedefi.com website (the “Website”) and governs data collection, processing and usage in compliance with the Personal Data Protection Act 2012 (No. 26 of 2012) of Singapore (“PDPA”).
By using the Website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
This Privacy Policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>